{"metadata": {"shape": [791, 1085, 3]}, "questions": [{"question": "day1", "answers": [{"value": 0, "coord": [39, 343], "filled": false}, {"value": 1, "coord": [38, 361], "filled": false}, {"value": 2, "coord": [38, 378], "filled": false}, {"value": 3, "coord": [38, 396], "filled": false}]}, {"question": "day2", "answers": [{"value": 0, "coord": [63, 343], "filled": false}, {"value": 1, "coord": [63, 361], "filled": false}, {"value": 2, "coord": [63, 378], "filled": false}, {"value": 3, "coord": [63, 396], "filled": false}, {"value": 4, "coord": [63, 413], "filled": false}, {"value": 5, "coord": [62, 431], "filled": false}, {"value": 6, "coord": [62, 448], "filled": false}, {"value": 7, "coord": [63, 466], "filled": false}, {"value": 8, "coord": [63, 483], "filled": false}, {"value": 9, "coord": [63, 501], "filled": false}]}, {"question": "month", "answers": [{"value": 1, "coord": [111, 343], "filled": false}, {"value": 2, "coord": [111, 361], "filled": false}, {"value": 3, "coord": [111, 378], "filled": false}, {"value": 4, "coord": [111, 396], "filled": false}, {"value": 5, "coord": [111, 413], "filled": false}, {"value": 6, "coord": [111, 431], "filled": false}, {"value": 7, "coord": [111, 448], "filled": false}, {"value": 8, "coord": [111, 466], "filled": false}, {"value": 9, "coord": [111, 483], "filled": false}, {"value": 10, "coord": [111, 500], "filled": false}, {"value": 11, "coord": [111, 518], "filled": false}, {"value": 12, "coord": [111, 535], "filled": false}]}, {"question": "year", "answers": [{"value": 2020, "coord": [160, 343], "filled": false}, {"value": 2021, "coord": [160, 361], "filled": false}, {"value": 2022, "coord": [160, 378], "filled": false}, {"value": 2023, "coord": [159, 396], "filled": false}, {"value": 2024, "coord": [159, 414], "filled": false}]}, {"question": "shift", "answers": [{"value": "AM", "coord": [208, 501], "filled": false}, {"value": "PM", "coord": [208, 518], "filled": false}]}, {"question": "cell", "answers": [{"value": "machined", "coord": [279, 500], "filled": false}, {"value": "isolast", "coord": [303, 500], "filled": false}, {"value": "custom", "coord": [232, 501], "filled": false}, {"value": "orings", "coord": [255, 501], "filled": false}, {"value": "bonded", "coord": [232, 518], "filled": false}, {"value": "flexVRings", "coord": [255, 518], "filled": false}, {"value": "silastics", "coord": [280, 518], "filled": false}, {"value": "cleanroom", "coord": [304, 518], "filled": false}]}, {"question": "press", "answers": [{"value": "press1", "coord": [303, 343], "filled": false}, {"value": "press5", "coord": [401, 343], "filled": false}, {"value": "press9", "coord": [497, 343], "filled": false}, {"value": "press13", "coord": [593, 343], "filled": false}, {"value": "press2", "coord": [303, 360], "filled": false}, {"value": "press6", "coord": [401, 360], "filled": false}, {"value": "press10", "coord": [497, 360], "filled": false}, {"value": "press14", "coord": [593, 361], "filled": false}, {"value": "press3", "coord": [303, 378], "filled": false}, {"value": "press7", "coord": [401, 378], "filled": false}, {"value": "press11", "coord": [497, 378], "filled": false}, {"value": "press15", "coord": [593, 378], "filled": false}, {"value": "press4", "coord": [401, 395], "filled": false}, {"value": "press8", "coord": [303, 396], "filled": false}, {"value": "press12", "coord": [497, 396], "filled": false}, {"value": "press16", "coord": [593, 396], "filled": false}]}, {"question": "hr1MOID", "answers": [{"value": 1, "coord": [63, 605], "filled": false}, {"value": 2, "coord": [87, 606], "filled": false}, {"value": 3, "coord": [111, 605], "filled": false}, {"value": 4, "coord": [135, 605], "filled": false}, {"value": 5, "coord": [160, 605], "filled": false}, {"value": 6, "coord": [184, 605], "filled": false}]}, {"question": "hr2MOID", "answers": [{"value": 1, "coord": [63, 623], "filled": false}, {"value": 2, "coord": [87, 623], "filled": false}, {"value": 3, "coord": [111, 623], "filled": false}, {"value": 4, "coord": [135, 623], "filled": false}, {"value": 5, "coord": [160, 623], "filled": false}, {"value": 6, "coord": [184, 623], "filled": false}]}, {"question": "hr3MOID", "answers": [{"value": 1, "coord": [63, 641], "filled": false}, {"value": 2, "coord": [87, 641], "filled": false}, {"value": 3, "coord": [111, 641], "filled": false}, {"value": 4, "coord": [135, 640], "filled": false}, {"value": 5, "coord": [160, 640], "filled": false}, {"value": 6, "coord": [184, 640], "filled": false}]}, {"question": "hr4MOID", "answers": [{"value": 1, "coord": [63, 658], "filled": false}, {"value": 2, "coord": [87, 658], "filled": false}, {"value": 3, "coord": [111, 658], "filled": false}, {"value": 4, "coord": [135, 658], "filled": false}, {"value": 5, "coord": [160, 658], "filled": false}, {"value": 6, "coord": [184, 658], "filled": false}]}, {"question": "hr5MOID", "answers": [{"value": 1, "coord": [63, 675], "filled": false}, {"value": 2, "coord": [87, 675], "filled": false}, {"value": 3, "coord": [111, 675], "filled": false}, {"value": 4, "coord": [135, 675], "filled": false}, {"value": 5, "coord": [160, 675], "filled": false}, {"value": 6, "coord": [184, 675], "filled": false}]}, {"question": "hr6MOID", "answers": [{"value": 1, "coord": [62, 692], "filled": false}, {"value": 2, "coord": [87, 692], "filled": false}, {"value": 3, "coord": [111, 692], "filled": false}, {"value": 4, "coord": [135, 692], "filled": false}, {"value": 5, "coord": [160, 692], "filled": false}, {"value": 6, "coord": [184, 692], "filled": false}]}, {"question": "hr7MOID", "answers": [{"value": 1, "coord": [62, 710], "filled": false}, {"value": 2, "coord": [87, 710], "filled": false}, {"value": 3, "coord": [111, 710], "filled": false}, {"value": 4, "coord": [135, 710], "filled": false}, {"value": 5, "coord": [160, 710], "filled": false}, {"value": 6, "coord": [184, 710], "filled": false}]}, {"question": "hr8MOID", "answers": [{"value": 1, "coord": [62, 727], "filled": false}, {"value": 2, "coord": [87, 727], "filled": false}, {"value": 3, "coord": [111, 727], "filled": false}, {"value": 4, "coord": [135, 727], "filled": false}, {"value": 5, "coord": [160, 727], "filled": false}, {"value": 6, "coord": [184, 727], "filled": false}]}, {"question": "hr9MOID", "answers": [{"value": 1, "coord": [62, 744], "filled": false}, {"value": 2, "coord": [87, 744], "filled": false}, {"value": 3, "coord": [111, 744], "filled": false}, {"value": 4, "coord": [135, 744], "filled": false}, {"value": 5, "coord": [160, 744], "filled": false}, {"value": 6, "coord": [184, 744], "filled": false}]}, {"question": "hr10MOID", "answers": [{"value": 1, "coord": [62, 761], "filled": false}, {"value": 2, "coord": [87, 761], "filled": false}, {"value": 3, "coord": [111, 761], "filled": false}, {"value": 4, "coord": [135, 761], "filled": false}, {"value": 5, "coord": [160, 761], "filled": false}, {"value": 6, "coord": [184, 761], "filled": false}]}, {"question": "hr1lifts", "answers": [{"value": 1, "coord": [211, 605], "filled": false}, {"value": 2, "coord": [234, 605], "filled": false}, {"value": 3, "coord": [258, 605], "filled": false}, {"value": 4, "coord": [282, 605], "filled": false}, {"value": 5, "coord": [306, 605], "filled": false}, {"value": 6, "coord": [330, 605], "filled": false}, {"value": 7, "coord": [355, 605], "filled": false}, {"value": 8, "coord": [379, 605], "filled": false}, {"value": 9, "coord": [403, 605], "filled": false}, {"value": 10, "coord": [427, 605], "filled": false}]}, {"question": "hr2lifts", "answers": [{"value": 1, "coord": [211, 623], "filled": false}, {"value": 2, "coord": [234, 623], "filled": false}, {"value": 3, "coord": [258, 623], "filled": false}, {"value": 4, "coord": [282, 623], "filled": false}, {"value": 5, "coord": [306, 623], "filled": false}, {"value": 6, "coord": [330, 623], "filled": false}, {"value": 7, "coord": [354, 623], "filled": false}, {"value": 8, "coord": [379, 623], "filled": false}, {"value": 9, "coord": [403, 622], "filled": false}, {"value": 10, "coord": [427, 622], "filled": false}]}, {"question": "hr3lifts", "answers": [{"value": 1, "coord": [211, 641], "filled": false}, {"value": 2, "coord": [234, 641], "filled": false}, {"value": 3, "coord": [257, 641], "filled": false}, {"value": 4, "coord": [282, 641], "filled": false}, {"value": 5, "coord": [306, 641], "filled": false}, {"value": 6, "coord": [330, 640], "filled": false}, {"value": 7, "coord": [354, 640], "filled": false}, {"value": 8, "coord": [379, 640], "filled": false}, {"value": 9, "coord": [403, 640], "filled": false}, {"value": 10, "coord": [427, 640], "filled": false}]}, {"question": "hr4lifts", "answers": [{"value": 1, "coord": [210, 658], "filled": false}, {"value": 2, "coord": [234, 658], "filled": false}, {"value": 3, "coord": [257, 658], "filled": false}, {"value": 4, "coord": [282, 658], "filled": false}, {"value": 5, "coord": [306, 658], "filled": false}, {"value": 6, "coord": [330, 658], "filled": false}, {"value": 7, "coord": [355, 658], "filled": false}, {"value": 8, "coord": [379, 658], "filled": false}, {"value": 9, "coord": [403, 658], "filled": false}, {"value": 10, "coord": [427, 657], "filled": false}]}, {"question": "hr5lifts", "answers": [{"value": 1, "coord": [210, 675], "filled": false}, {"value": 2, "coord": [234, 675], "filled": false}, {"value": 3, "coord": [257, 675], "filled": false}, {"value": 4, "coord": [282, 675], "filled": false}, {"value": 5, "coord": [306, 675], "filled": false}, {"value": 6, "coord": [330, 675], "filled": false}, {"value": 7, "coord": [355, 675], "filled": false}, {"value": 8, "coord": [379, 675], "filled": false}, {"value": 9, "coord": [403, 675], "filled": false}, {"value": 10, "coord": [427, 674], "filled": false}]}, {"question": "hr6lifts", "answers": [{"value": 1, "coord": [210, 692], "filled": false}, {"value": 2, "coord": [234, 693], "filled": false}, {"value": 3, "coord": [258, 693], "filled": false}, {"value": 4, "coord": [282, 692], "filled": false}, {"value": 5, "coord": [306, 692], "filled": false}, {"value": 6, "coord": [330, 692], "filled": false}, {"value": 7, "coord": [355, 692], "filled": false}, {"value": 8, "coord": [379, 692], "filled": false}, {"value": 9, "coord": [403, 692], "filled": false}, {"value": 10, "coord": [427, 692], "filled": false}]}, {"question": "hr7lifts", "answers": [{"value": 1, "coord": [210, 710], "filled": false}, {"value": 2, "coord": [234, 710], "filled": false}, {"value": 3, "coord": [258, 710], "filled": false}, {"value": 4, "coord": [282, 710], "filled": false}, {"value": 5, "coord": [306, 710], "filled": false}, {"value": 6, "coord": [330, 710], "filled": false}, {"value": 7, "coord": [355, 709], "filled": false}, {"value": 8, "coord": [379, 709], "filled": false}, {"value": 9, "coord": [403, 709], "filled": false}, {"value": 10, "coord": [427, 709], "filled": false}]}, {"question": "hr8lifts", "answers": [{"value": 1, "coord": [210, 727], "filled": false}, {"value": 2, "coord": [234, 727], "filled": false}, {"value": 3, "coord": [258, 727], "filled": false}, {"value": 4, "coord": [282, 727], "filled": false}, {"value": 5, "coord": [306, 727], "filled": false}, {"value": 6, "coord": [330, 727], "filled": false}, {"value": 7, "coord": [355, 727], "filled": false}, {"value": 8, "coord": [379, 727], "filled": false}, {"value": 9, "coord": [403, 727], "filled": false}, {"value": 10, "coord": [427, 726], "filled": false}]}, {"question": "hr9lifts", "answers": [{"value": 1, "coord": [211, 744], "filled": false}, {"value": 2, "coord": [234, 744], "filled": false}, {"value": 3, "coord": [258, 744], "filled": false}, {"value": 4, "coord": [282, 744], "filled": false}, {"value": 5, "coord": [306, 744], "filled": false}, {"value": 6, "coord": [330, 744], "filled": false}, {"value": 7, "coord": [355, 744], "filled": false}, {"value": 8, "coord": [379, 744], "filled": false}, {"value": 9, "coord": [403, 744], "filled": false}, {"value": 10, "coord": [427, 744], "filled": false}]}, {"question": "hr10lifts", "answers": [{"value": 1, "coord": [211, 762], "filled": false}, {"value": 2, "coord": [234, 762], "filled": false}, {"value": 3, "coord": [258, 762], "filled": false}, {"value": 4, "coord": [282, 762], "filled": false}, {"value": 5, "coord": [306, 762], "filled": false}, {"value": 6, "coord": [330, 761], "filled": false}, {"value": 7, "coord": [355, 761], "filled": false}, {"value": 8, "coord": [379, 761], "filled": false}, {"value": 9, "coord": [403, 761], "filled": false}, {"value": 10, "coord": [428, 761], "filled": false}]}, {"question": "hr1downtime", "answers": [{"value": "A", "coord": [451, 605], "filled": false}, {"value": "B", "coord": [475, 605], "filled": false}, {"value": "C", "coord": [499, 605], "filled": false}, {"value": "D", "coord": [523, 605], "filled": false}, {"value": "E", "coord": [547, 605], "filled": false}, {"value": "F", "coord": [571, 605], "filled": false}, {"value": "G", "coord": [595, 605], "filled": false}]}, {"question": "hr2downtime", "answers": [{"value": "A", "coord": [451, 622], "filled": false}, {"value": "B", "coord": [475, 623], "filled": false}, {"value": "C", "coord": [499, 623], "filled": false}, {"value": "D", "coord": [523, 623], "filled": false}, {"value": "E", "coord": [547, 623], "filled": false}, {"value": "F", "coord": [571, 623], "filled": false}, {"value": "G", "coord": [596, 623], "filled": false}]}, {"question": "hr3downtime", "answers": [{"value": "A", "coord": [451, 640], "filled": false}, {"value": "B", "coord": [475, 640], "filled": false}, {"value": "C", "coord": [499, 640], "filled": false}, {"value": "D", "coord": [523, 640], "filled": false}, {"value": "E", "coord": [547, 640], "filled": false}, {"value": "F", "coord": [571, 640], "filled": false}, {"value": "G", "coord": [596, 641], "filled": false}]}, {"question": "hr4downtime", "answers": [{"value": "A", "coord": [451, 658], "filled": false}, {"value": "B", "coord": [475, 658], "filled": false}, {"value": "C", "coord": [499, 658], "filled": false}, {"value": "D", "coord": [523, 658], "filled": false}, {"value": "E", "coord": [547, 658], "filled": false}, {"value": "F", "coord": [571, 658], "filled": false}, {"value": "G", "coord": [596, 658], "filled": false}]}, {"question": "hr5downtime", "answers": [{"value": "A", "coord": [451, 674], "filled": false}, {"value": "B", "coord": [475, 675], "filled": false}, {"value": "C", "coord": [499, 675], "filled": false}, {"value": "D", "coord": [523, 675], "filled": false}, {"value": "E", "coord": [547, 675], "filled": false}, {"value": "F", "coord": [571, 675], "filled": false}, {"value": "G", "coord": [596, 675], "filled": false}]}, {"question": "hr6downtime", "answers": [{"value": "A", "coord": [451, 692], "filled": false}, {"value": "B", "coord": [475, 692], "filled": false}, {"value": "C", "coord": [499, 692], "filled": false}, {"value": "D", "coord": [523, 692], "filled": false}, {"value": "E", "coord": [547, 692], "filled": false}, {"value": "F", "coord": [571, 692], "filled": false}, {"value": "G", "coord": [596, 692], "filled": false}]}, {"question": "hr7downtime", "answers": [{"value": "A", "coord": [451, 709], "filled": false}, {"value": "B", "coord": [475, 710], "filled": false}, {"value": "C", "coord": [499, 710], "filled": false}, {"value": "D", "coord": [523, 710], "filled": false}, {"value": "E", "coord": [547, 710], "filled": false}, {"value": "F", "coord": [571, 709], "filled": false}, {"value": "G", "coord": [596, 710], "filled": false}]}, {"question": "hr8downtime", "answers": [{"value": "A", "coord": [452, 727], "filled": false}, {"value": "B", "coord": [475, 727], "filled": false}, {"value": "C", "coord": [499, 727], "filled": false}, {"value": "D", "coord": [523, 727], "filled": false}, {"value": "E", "coord": [547, 727], "filled": false}, {"value": "F", "coord": [571, 727], "filled": false}, {"value": "G", "coord": [596, 727], "filled": false}]}, {"question": "hr9downtime", "answers": [{"value": "A", "coord": [452, 744], "filled": false}, {"value": "B", "coord": [475, 744], "filled": false}, {"value": "C", "coord": [499, 744], "filled": false}, {"value": "D", "coord": [523, 744], "filled": false}, {"value": "E", "coord": [547, 744], "filled": false}, {"value": "F", "coord": [571, 744], "filled": false}, {"value": "G", "coord": [596, 744], "filled": false}]}, {"question": "hr10downtime", "answers": [{"value": "A", "coord": [452, 761], "filled": false}, {"value": "B", "coord": [476, 762], "filled": false}, {"value": "C", "coord": [499, 762], "filled": false}, {"value": "D", "coord": [523, 762], "filled": false}, {"value": "E", "coord": [547, 761], "filled": false}, {"value": "F", "coord": [571, 761], "filled": false}, {"value": "G", "coord": [596, 762], "filled": false}]}, {"question": "moid1Pre", "answers": [{"value": "ORI", "coord": [677, 132], "filled": false}, {"value": "IAO", "coord": [677, 150], "filled": false}, {"value": "MCS", "coord": [677, 167], "filled": false}, {"value": "SIL", "coord": [677, 185], "filled": false}, {"value": "SEA", "coord": [677, 203], "filled": false}, {"value": "BON", "coord": [677, 220], "filled": false}, {"value": "BOM", "coord": [677, 238], "filled": false}, {"value": "CMO", "coord": [676, 255], "filled": false}, {"value": "SFALL", "coord": [676, 273], "filled": false}, {"value": "FAIR", "coord": [676, 290], "filled": false}]}, {"question": "moid1Suf1", "answers": [{"value": 0, "coord": [701, 132], "filled": false}, {"value": 1, "coord": [701, 150], "filled": false}, {"value": 2, "coord": [701, 167], "filled": false}, {"value": 3, "coord": [701, 185], "filled": false}, {"value": 4, "coord": [701, 203], "filled": false}, {"value": 5, "coord": [701, 220], "filled": false}, {"value": 6, "coord": [701, 238], "filled": false}, {"value": 7, "coord": [701, 255], "filled": false}, {"value": 8, "coord": [701, 273], "filled": false}, {"value": 9, "coord": [701, 290], "filled": false}]}, {"question": "moid1Suf2", "answers": [{"value": 0, "coord": [725, 132], "filled": false}, {"value": 1, "coord": [725, 150], "filled": false}, {"value": 2, "coord": [725, 167], "filled": false}, {"value": 3, "coord": [725, 185], "filled": false}, {"value": 4, "coord": [725, 203], "filled": false}, {"value": 5, "coord": [725, 220], "filled": false}, {"value": 6, "coord": [725, 238], "filled": false}, {"value": 7, "coord": [724, 255], "filled": false}, {"value": 8, "coord": [725, 273], "filled": false}, {"value": 9, "coord": [725, 290], "filled": false}]}, {"question": "moid1Suf3", "answers": [{"value": 0, "coord": [749, 132], "filled": false}, {"value": 1, "coord": [749, 150], "filled": false}, {"value": 2, "coord": [749, 167], "filled": false}, {"value": 3, "coord": [749, 185], "filled": false}, {"value": 4, "coord": [749, 202], "filled": false}, {"value": 5, "coord": [749, 220], "filled": false}, {"value": 6, "coord": [749, 238], "filled": false}, {"value": 7, "coord": [749, 255], "filled": false}, {"value": 8, "coord": [749, 273], "filled": false}, {"value": 9, "coord": [749, 290], "filled": false}]}, {"question": "moid1Cav1", "answers": [{"value": 0, "coord": [773, 132], "filled": false}, {"value": 1, "coord": [773, 150], "filled": false}, {"value": 2, "coord": [773, 167], "filled": false}, {"value": 3, "coord": [773, 185], "filled": false}, {"value": 4, "coord": [773, 202], "filled": false}, {"value": 5, "coord": [773, 220], "filled": false}, {"value": 6, "coord": [773, 238], "filled": false}, {"value": 7, "coord": [773, 255], "filled": false}, {"value": 8, "coord": [773, 273], "filled": false}, {"value": 9, "coord": [773, 290], "filled": false}]}, {"question": "moid1Cav2", "answers": [{"value": 0, "coord": [797, 132], "filled": false}, {"value": 1, "coord": [797, 150], "filled": false}, {"value": 2, "coord": [797, 167], "filled": false}, {"value": 3, "coord": [797, 185], "filled": false}, {"value": 4, "coord": [797, 203], "filled": false}, {"value": 5, "coord": [797, 220], "filled": false}, {"value": 6, "coord": [797, 238], "filled": false}, {"value": 7, "coord": [797, 255], "filled": false}, {"value": 8, "coord": [797, 273], "filled": false}, {"value": 9, "coord": [797, 290], "filled": false}]}, {"question": "moid1Cav3", "answers": [{"value": 0, "coord": [821, 132], "filled": false}, {"value": 1, "coord": [820, 150], "filled": false}, {"value": 2, "coord": [821, 167], "filled": false}, {"value": 3, "coord": [821, 185], "filled": false}, {"value": 4, "coord": [821, 203], "filled": false}, {"value": 5, "coord": [821, 220], "filled": false}, {"value": 6, "coord": [821, 238], "filled": false}, {"value": 7, "coord": [820, 255], "filled": false}, {"value": 8, "coord": [820, 273], "filled": false}, {"value": 9, "coord": [820, 290], "filled": false}]}, {"question": "moid2Pre", "answers": [{"value": "ORI", "coord": [905, 132], "filled": false}, {"value": "IAO", "coord": [904, 150], "filled": false}, {"value": "MCS", "coord": [904, 167], "filled": false}, {"value": "SIL", "coord": [904, 185], "filled": false}, {"value": "SEA", "coord": [904, 203], "filled": false}, {"value": "BON", "coord": [904, 220], "filled": false}, {"value": "BOM", "coord": [904, 238], "filled": false}, {"value": "CMO", "coord": [904, 255], "filled": false}, {"value": "SFALL", "coord": [904, 273], "filled": false}, {"value": "FAIR", "coord": [904, 290], "filled": false}]}, {"question": "moid2Suf1", "answers": [{"value": 0, "coord": [929, 132], "filled": false}, {"value": 1, "coord": [928, 150], "filled": false}, {"value": 2, "coord": [928, 167], "filled": false}, {"value": 3, "coord": [929, 185], "filled": false}, {"value": 4, "coord": [929, 203], "filled": false}, {"value": 5, "coord": [929, 220], "filled": false}, {"value": 6, "coord": [929, 238], "filled": false}, {"value": 7, "coord": [928, 255], "filled": false}, {"value": 8, "coord": [928, 273], "filled": false}, {"value": 9, "coord": [928, 290], "filled": false}]}, {"question": "moid2Suf2", "answers": [{"value": 0, "coord": [953, 132], "filled": false}, {"value": 1, "coord": [953, 150], "filled": false}, {"value": 2, "coord": [953, 168], "filled": false}, {"value": 3, "coord": [953, 185], "filled": false}, {"value": 4, "coord": [953, 203], "filled": false}, {"value": 5, "coord": [953, 220], "filled": false}, {"value": 6, "coord": [953, 238], "filled": false}, {"value": 7, "coord": [953, 255], "filled": false}, {"value": 8, "coord": [952, 273], "filled": false}, {"value": 9, "coord": [953, 290], "filled": false}]}, {"question": "moid2Suf3", "answers": [{"value": 0, "coord": [977, 132], "filled": false}, {"value": 1, "coord": [977, 150], "filled": false}, {"value": 2, "coord": [977, 168], "filled": false}, {"value": 3, "coord": [977, 185], "filled": false}, {"value": 4, "coord": [977, 203], "filled": false}, {"value": 5, "coord": [977, 220], "filled": false}, {"value": 6, "coord": [977, 238], "filled": false}, {"value": 7, "coord": [977, 256], "filled": false}, {"value": 8, "coord": [977, 273], "filled": false}, {"value": 9, "coord": [977, 291], "filled": false}]}, {"question": "moid2Cav1", "answers": [{"value": 0, "coord": [1001, 132], "filled": false}, {"value": 1, "coord": [1001, 150], "filled": false}, {"value": 2, "coord": [1001, 168], "filled": false}, {"value": 3, "coord": [1001, 185], "filled": false}, {"value": 4, "coord": [1001, 203], "filled": false}, {"value": 5, "coord": [1001, 220], "filled": false}, {"value": 6, "coord": [1001, 238], "filled": false}, {"value": 7, "coord": [1001, 256], "filled": false}, {"value": 8, "coord": [1001, 273], "filled": false}, {"value": 9, "coord": [1001, 291], "filled": false}]}, {"question": "moid2Cav2", "answers": [{"value": 0, "coord": [1025, 132], "filled": false}, {"value": 1, "coord": [1025, 150], "filled": false}, {"value": 2, "coord": [1025, 168], "filled": false}, {"value": 3, "coord": [1025, 185], "filled": false}, {"value": 4, "coord": [1025, 203], "filled": false}, {"value": 5, "coord": [1025, 220], "filled": false}, {"value": 6, "coord": [1025, 238], "filled": false}, {"value": 7, "coord": [1025, 256], "filled": false}, {"value": 8, "coord": [1025, 273], "filled": false}, {"value": 9, "coord": [1025, 291], "filled": false}]}, {"question": "moid2Cav3", "answers": [{"value": 0, "coord": [1049, 132], "filled": false}, {"value": 1, "coord": [1049, 150], "filled": false}, {"value": 2, "coord": [1049, 168], "filled": false}, {"value": 3, "coord": [1049, 185], "filled": false}, {"value": 4, "coord": [1049, 203], "filled": false}, {"value": 5, "coord": [1049, 220], "filled": false}, {"value": 6, "coord": [1049, 238], "filled": false}, {"value": 7, "coord": [1049, 256], "filled": false}, {"value": 8, "coord": [1049, 273], "filled": false}, {"value": 9, "coord": [1049, 291], "filled": false}]}, {"question": "moid3Pre", "answers": [{"value": "ORI", "coord": [677, 360], "filled": false}, {"value": "IAO", "coord": [677, 378], "filled": false}, {"value": "MCS", "coord": [677, 396], "filled": false}, {"value": "SIL", "coord": [677, 413], "filled": false}, {"value": "SEA", "coord": [677, 431], "filled": false}, {"value": "BON", "coord": [677, 448], "filled": false}, {"value": "BOM", "coord": [677, 465], "filled": false}, {"value": "CMO", "coord": [677, 483], "filled": false}, {"value": "SFALL", "coord": [676, 500], "filled": false}, {"value": "FAIR", "coord": [676, 518], "filled": false}]}, {"question": "moid3Suf1", "answers": [{"value": 0, "coord": [701, 360], "filled": false}, {"value": 1, "coord": [701, 378], "filled": false}, {"value": 2, "coord": [701, 396], "filled": false}, {"value": 3, "coord": [701, 413], "filled": false}, {"value": 4, "coord": [701, 431], "filled": false}, {"value": 5, "coord": [701, 448], "filled": false}, {"value": 6, "coord": [701, 465], "filled": false}, {"value": 7, "coord": [701, 483], "filled": false}, {"value": 8, "coord": [701, 500], "filled": false}, {"value": 9, "coord": [701, 518], "filled": false}]}, {"question": "moid3Suf2", "answers": [{"value": 0, "coord": [725, 360], "filled": false}, {"value": 1, "coord": [725, 378], "filled": false}, {"value": 2, "coord": [725, 395], "filled": false}, {"value": 3, "coord": [725, 413], "filled": false}, {"value": 4, "coord": [725, 431], "filled": false}, {"value": 5, "coord": [725, 448], "filled": false}, {"value": 6, "coord": [725, 465], "filled": false}, {"value": 7, "coord": [725, 483], "filled": false}, {"value": 8, "coord": [725, 500], "filled": false}, {"value": 9, "coord": [725, 518], "filled": false}]}, {"question": "moid3Suf3", "answers": [{"value": 0, "coord": [749, 360], "filled": false}, {"value": 1, "coord": [749, 378], "filled": false}, {"value": 2, "coord": [749, 395], "filled": false}, {"value": 3, "coord": [749, 413], "filled": false}, {"value": 4, "coord": [749, 431], "filled": false}, {"value": 5, "coord": [749, 448], "filled": false}, {"value": 6, "coord": [749, 465], "filled": false}, {"value": 7, "coord": [749, 483], "filled": false}, {"value": 8, "coord": [749, 500], "filled": false}, {"value": 9, "coord": [749, 518], "filled": false}]}, {"question": "moid3Cav1", "answers": [{"value": 0, "coord": [773, 360], "filled": false}, {"value": 1, "coord": [773, 378], "filled": false}, {"value": 2, "coord": [773, 395], "filled": false}, {"value": 3, "coord": [773, 413], "filled": false}, {"value": 4, "coord": [773, 431], "filled": false}, {"value": 5, "coord": [773, 448], "filled": false}, {"value": 6, "coord": [773, 465], "filled": false}, {"value": 7, "coord": [773, 483], "filled": false}, {"value": 8, "coord": [773, 500], "filled": false}, {"value": 9, "coord": [773, 518], "filled": false}]}, {"question": "moid3Cav2", "answers": [{"value": 0, "coord": [797, 360], "filled": false}, {"value": 1, "coord": [797, 378], "filled": false}, {"value": 2, "coord": [797, 395], "filled": false}, {"value": 3, "coord": [797, 413], "filled": false}, {"value": 4, "coord": [797, 430], "filled": false}, {"value": 5, "coord": [797, 448], "filled": false}, {"value": 6, "coord": [797, 465], "filled": false}, {"value": 7, "coord": [797, 483], "filled": false}, {"value": 8, "coord": [797, 500], "filled": false}, {"value": 9, "coord": [797, 517], "filled": false}]}, {"question": "moid3Cav3", "answers": [{"value": 0, "coord": [821, 360], "filled": false}, {"value": 1, "coord": [821, 378], "filled": false}, {"value": 2, "coord": [821, 395], "filled": false}, {"value": 3, "coord": [821, 413], "filled": false}, {"value": 4, "coord": [821, 430], "filled": false}, {"value": 5, "coord": [821, 448], "filled": false}, {"value": 6, "coord": [821, 465], "filled": false}, {"value": 7, "coord": [821, 483], "filled": false}, {"value": 8, "coord": [820, 500], "filled": false}, {"value": 9, "coord": [820, 517], "filled": false}]}, {"question": "moid4Pre", "answers": [{"value": "ORI", "coord": [904, 360], "filled": false}, {"value": "IAO", "coord": [904, 378], "filled": false}, {"value": "MCS", "coord": [904, 395], "filled": false}, {"value": "SIL", "coord": [904, 413], "filled": false}, {"value": "SEA", "coord": [904, 431], "filled": false}, {"value": "BON", "coord": [904, 448], "filled": false}, {"value": "BOM", "coord": [904, 465], "filled": false}, {"value": "CMO", "coord": [905, 483], "filled": false}, {"value": "SFALL", "coord": [905, 500], "filled": false}, {"value": "FAIR", "coord": [904, 518], "filled": false}]}, {"question": "moid4Suf1", "answers": [{"value": 0, "coord": [928, 360], "filled": false}, {"value": 1, "coord": [928, 378], "filled": false}, {"value": 2, "coord": [929, 396], "filled": false}, {"value": 3, "coord": [929, 413], "filled": false}, {"value": 4, "coord": [929, 431], "filled": false}, {"value": 5, "coord": [929, 448], "filled": false}, {"value": 6, "coord": [929, 465], "filled": false}, {"value": 7, "coord": [929, 483], "filled": false}, {"value": 8, "coord": [929, 500], "filled": false}, {"value": 9, "coord": [928, 518], "filled": false}]}, {"question": "moid4Suf2", "answers": [{"value": 0, "coord": [953, 360], "filled": false}, {"value": 1, "coord": [953, 378], "filled": false}, {"value": 2, "coord": [953, 395], "filled": false}, {"value": 3, "coord": [953, 413], "filled": false}, {"value": 4, "coord": [953, 431], "filled": false}, {"value": 5, "coord": [953, 448], "filled": false}, {"value": 6, "coord": [953, 465], "filled": false}, {"value": 7, "coord": [953, 483], "filled": false}, {"value": 8, "coord": [953, 500], "filled": false}, {"value": 9, "coord": [953, 518], "filled": false}]}, {"question": "moid4Suf3", "answers": [{"value": 0, "coord": [977, 361], "filled": false}, {"value": 1, "coord": [977, 378], "filled": false}, {"value": 2, "coord": [977, 396], "filled": false}, {"value": 3, "coord": [977, 413], "filled": false}, {"value": 4, "coord": [977, 431], "filled": false}, {"value": 5, "coord": [977, 448], "filled": false}, {"value": 6, "coord": [977, 465], "filled": false}, {"value": 7, "coord": [977, 483], "filled": false}, {"value": 8, "coord": [977, 501], "filled": false}, {"value": 9, "coord": [977, 518], "filled": false}]}, {"question": "moid4Cav1", "answers": [{"value": 0, "coord": [1001, 361], "filled": false}, {"value": 1, "coord": [1001, 378], "filled": false}, {"value": 2, "coord": [1001, 396], "filled": false}, {"value": 3, "coord": [1001, 413], "filled": false}, {"value": 4, "coord": [1001, 431], "filled": false}, {"value": 5, "coord": [1001, 448], "filled": false}, {"value": 6, "coord": [1001, 466], "filled": false}, {"value": 7, "coord": [1001, 483], "filled": false}, {"value": 8, "coord": [1001, 501], "filled": false}, {"value": 9, "coord": [1001, 518], "filled": false}]}, {"question": "moid4Cav2", "answers": [{"value": 0, "coord": [1025, 361], "filled": false}, {"value": 1, "coord": [1025, 378], "filled": false}, {"value": 2, "coord": [1025, 396], "filled": false}, {"value": 3, "coord": [1025, 413], "filled": false}, {"value": 4, "coord": [1025, 431], "filled": false}, {"value": 5, "coord": [1025, 448], "filled": false}, {"value": 6, "coord": [1025, 466], "filled": false}, {"value": 7, "coord": [1025, 483], "filled": false}, {"value": 8, "coord": [1025, 501], "filled": false}, {"value": 9, "coord": [1025, 518], "filled": false}]}, {"question": "moid4Cav3", "answers": [{"value": 0, "coord": [1049, 361], "filled": false}, {"value": 1, "coord": [1049, 378], "filled": false}, {"value": 2, "coord": [1049, 396], "filled": false}, {"value": 3, "coord": [1049, 413], "filled": false}, {"value": 4, "coord": [1049, 431], "filled": false}, {"value": 5, "coord": [1049, 448], "filled": false}, {"value": 6, "coord": [1049, 466], "filled": false}, {"value": 7, "coord": [1049, 483], "filled": false}, {"value": 8, "coord": [1049, 501], "filled": false}, {"value": 9, "coord": [1049, 518], "filled": false}]}, {"question": "moid5Pre", "answers": [{"value": "ORI", "coord": [676, 588], "filled": false}, {"value": "IAO", "coord": [676, 605], "filled": false}, {"value": "MCS", "coord": [676, 623], "filled": false}, {"value": "SIL", "coord": [676, 640], "filled": false}, {"value": "SEA", "coord": [676, 658], "filled": false}, {"value": "BON", "coord": [676, 675], "filled": false}, {"value": "BOM", "coord": [676, 692], "filled": false}, {"value": "CMO", "coord": [676, 710], "filled": false}, {"value": "SFALL", "coord": [676, 727], "filled": false}, {"value": "FAIR", "coord": [676, 744], "filled": false}]}, {"question": "moid5Suf1", "answers": [{"value": 0, "coord": [700, 588], "filled": false}, {"value": 1, "coord": [700, 605], "filled": false}, {"value": 2, "coord": [700, 623], "filled": false}, {"value": 3, "coord": [701, 640], "filled": false}, {"value": 4, "coord": [701, 658], "filled": false}, {"value": 5, "coord": [701, 675], "filled": false}, {"value": 6, "coord": [701, 692], "filled": false}, {"value": 7, "coord": [701, 710], "filled": false}, {"value": 8, "coord": [701, 727], "filled": false}, {"value": 9, "coord": [701, 744], "filled": false}]}, {"question": "moid5Suf2", "answers": [{"value": 0, "coord": [724, 588], "filled": false}, {"value": 1, "coord": [724, 605], "filled": false}, {"value": 2, "coord": [724, 623], "filled": false}, {"value": 3, "coord": [724, 640], "filled": false}, {"value": 4, "coord": [724, 658], "filled": false}, {"value": 5, "coord": [724, 675], "filled": false}, {"value": 6, "coord": [724, 692], "filled": false}, {"value": 7, "coord": [724, 709], "filled": false}, {"value": 8, "coord": [724, 727], "filled": false}, {"value": 9, "coord": [725, 744], "filled": false}]}, {"question": "moid5Suf3", "answers": [{"value": 0, "coord": [749, 588], "filled": false}, {"value": 1, "coord": [749, 605], "filled": false}, {"value": 2, "coord": [749, 623], "filled": false}, {"value": 3, "coord": [749, 640], "filled": false}, {"value": 4, "coord": [749, 658], "filled": false}, {"value": 5, "coord": [749, 675], "filled": false}, {"value": 6, "coord": [749, 692], "filled": false}, {"value": 7, "coord": [749, 710], "filled": false}, {"value": 8, "coord": [749, 727], "filled": false}, {"value": 9, "coord": [749, 744], "filled": false}]}, {"question": "moid5Cav1", "answers": [{"value": 0, "coord": [773, 588], "filled": false}, {"value": 1, "coord": [772, 605], "filled": false}, {"value": 2, "coord": [773, 623], "filled": false}, {"value": 3, "coord": [773, 640], "filled": false}, {"value": 4, "coord": [773, 658], "filled": false}, {"value": 5, "coord": [773, 675], "filled": false}, {"value": 6, "coord": [772, 692], "filled": false}, {"value": 7, "coord": [773, 710], "filled": false}, {"value": 8, "coord": [773, 727], "filled": false}, {"value": 9, "coord": [773, 744], "filled": false}]}, {"question": "moid5Cav2", "answers": [{"value": 0, "coord": [797, 588], "filled": false}, {"value": 1, "coord": [796, 605], "filled": false}, {"value": 2, "coord": [796, 623], "filled": false}, {"value": 3, "coord": [796, 640], "filled": false}, {"value": 4, "coord": [796, 658], "filled": false}, {"value": 5, "coord": [796, 675], "filled": false}, {"value": 6, "coord": [796, 692], "filled": false}, {"value": 7, "coord": [796, 709], "filled": false}, {"value": 8, "coord": [796, 727], "filled": false}, {"value": 9, "coord": [796, 744], "filled": false}]}, {"question": "moid5Cav3", "answers": [{"value": 0, "coord": [820, 587], "filled": false}, {"value": 1, "coord": [820, 605], "filled": false}, {"value": 2, "coord": [820, 623], "filled": false}, {"value": 3, "coord": [820, 640], "filled": false}, {"value": 4, "coord": [820, 658], "filled": false}, {"value": 5, "coord": [820, 675], "filled": false}, {"value": 6, "coord": [820, 692], "filled": false}, {"value": 7, "coord": [820, 709], "filled": false}, {"value": 8, "coord": [820, 727], "filled": false}, {"value": 9, "coord": [820, 744], "filled": false}]}, {"question": "moid6Pre", "answers": [{"value": "ORI", "coord": [904, 588], "filled": false}, {"value": "IAO", "coord": [904, 605], "filled": false}, {"value": "MCS", "coord": [904, 623], "filled": false}, {"value": "SIL", "coord": [904, 640], "filled": false}, {"value": "SEA", "coord": [904, 658], "filled": false}, {"value": "BON", "coord": [904, 675], "filled": false}, {"value": "BOM", "coord": [904, 692], "filled": false}, {"value": "CMO", "coord": [904, 710], "filled": false}, {"value": "SFALL", "coord": [904, 727], "filled": false}, {"value": "FAIR", "coord": [904, 744], "filled": false}]}, {"question": "moid6Suf1", "answers": [{"value": 0, "coord": [928, 588], "filled": false}, {"value": 1, "coord": [928, 605], "filled": false}, {"value": 2, "coord": [928, 623], "filled": false}, {"value": 3, "coord": [928, 640], "filled": false}, {"value": 4, "coord": [928, 658], "filled": false}, {"value": 5, "coord": [928, 675], "filled": false}, {"value": 6, "coord": [928, 692], "filled": false}, {"value": 7, "coord": [928, 710], "filled": false}, {"value": 8, "coord": [928, 727], "filled": false}, {"value": 9, "coord": [928, 744], "filled": false}]}, {"question": "moid6Suf2", "answers": [{"value": 0, "coord": [953, 588], "filled": false}, {"value": 1, "coord": [953, 605], "filled": false}, {"value": 2, "coord": [952, 623], "filled": false}, {"value": 3, "coord": [952, 640], "filled": false}, {"value": 4, "coord": [952, 658], "filled": false}, {"value": 5, "coord": [952, 675], "filled": false}, {"value": 6, "coord": [952, 692], "filled": false}, {"value": 7, "coord": [952, 710], "filled": false}, {"value": 8, "coord": [952, 727], "filled": false}, {"value": 9, "coord": [952, 744], "filled": false}]}, {"question": "moid6Suf3", "answers": [{"value": 0, "coord": [977, 588], "filled": false}, {"value": 1, "coord": [977, 606], "filled": false}, {"value": 2, "coord": [977, 623], "filled": false}, {"value": 3, "coord": [976, 641], "filled": false}, {"value": 4, "coord": [977, 658], "filled": false}, {"value": 5, "coord": [976, 675], "filled": false}, {"value": 6, "coord": [976, 693], "filled": false}, {"value": 7, "coord": [976, 710], "filled": false}, {"value": 8, "coord": [976, 727], "filled": false}, {"value": 9, "coord": [977, 744], "filled": false}]}, {"question": "moid6Cav1", "answers": [{"value": 0, "coord": [1001, 588], "filled": false}, {"value": 1, "coord": [1001, 606], "filled": false}, {"value": 2, "coord": [1001, 623], "filled": false}, {"value": 3, "coord": [1000, 641], "filled": false}, {"value": 4, "coord": [1000, 658], "filled": false}, {"value": 5, "coord": [1000, 675], "filled": false}, {"value": 6, "coord": [1000, 693], "filled": false}, {"value": 7, "coord": [1000, 710], "filled": false}, {"value": 8, "coord": [1000, 727], "filled": false}, {"value": 9, "coord": [1000, 744], "filled": false}]}, {"question": "moid6Cav2", "answers": [{"value": 0, "coord": [1025, 588], "filled": false}, {"value": 1, "coord": [1025, 606], "filled": false}, {"value": 2, "coord": [1025, 623], "filled": false}, {"value": 3, "coord": [1025, 641], "filled": false}, {"value": 4, "coord": [1025, 658], "filled": false}, {"value": 5, "coord": [1025, 675], "filled": false}, {"value": 6, "coord": [1025, 693], "filled": false}, {"value": 7, "coord": [1025, 710], "filled": false}, {"value": 8, "coord": [1025, 727], "filled": false}, {"value": 9, "coord": [1025, 744], "filled": false}]}, {"question": "moid6Cav3", "answers": [{"value": 0, "coord": [1049, 588], "filled": false}, {"value": 1, "coord": [1049, 605], "filled": false}, {"value": 2, "coord": [1049, 623], "filled": false}, {"value": 3, "coord": [1049, 641], "filled": false}, {"value": 4, "coord": [1049, 658], "filled": false}, {"value": 5, "coord": [1049, 675], "filled": false}, {"value": 6, "coord": [1049, 692], "filled": false}, {"value": 7, "coord": [1049, 710], "filled": false}, {"value": 8, "coord": [1049, 727], "filled": false}, {"value": 9, "coord": [1049, 744], "filled": false}]}]}